castin.tv 2009-02-21

# Desi Videos - Castin.tv -Privacy Policy

The use of the Castin.TV website(s) and/or Castin.TV software and any Castin.TV services and products (collectively, the "Website") provided by Castin.TV Inc. ("Castin.TV") are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Castin.TV [Terms & Conditions](http://www.castin.tv/pages/terms.html). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.

**General**

Castin.TV takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. 

BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEBSITE), YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. Castin.TV reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Website following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms.

If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Website, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. 

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the Castin.TV website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.   
Collection of Information Personal Information. Use of certain features of the Website may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nickname (or other user ID) and a password. 

Non personally identifiable Information. Castin.TV may also collect or receive additional non-personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Website, and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on the Website.

Castin.TV may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the Website and pages are visited or when a Castin.TV client is used.

**How is the information being used?**

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by Castin.TV, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Website; and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

Please note that Castin.TV may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while Castin.TV's business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about Castin.TV users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. 

Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures, as determined by Castin.TV in good faith. Furthermore, Castin.TV may transfer personally identifiable information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Castin.TV or any of its websites or products, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy.

**Third Party Ad Servers**

Castin.TV or its advertisers may use other companies known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Website. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not Castin.TV's. 

**Non-UAE. Users**

The Website is operated and based in the United Arab Emirates. If you are accessing the Website from a jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations that differ from UAE laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United Arab Emirates and you consent to that transfer.
